{
    "id": "46e8be11e49a4c13a6188439fa1eb5f3",
    "title": "Active or passive voice exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "14182de7ba364ba398fb099bff9a3793",
            "title": "Active And Passive Voice Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Most things ………………….. plastic these days.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "made of",
                        "are made of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "My mother ……………….. wine from strawberries.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "makes",
                        "is made"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The house …………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is built",
                        "is being built"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "This bag …………………. of leather.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "made",
                        "is made"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "It ………………. disappeared. I can’t see it now.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "has been"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Their house ………………… last week.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "sold",
                        "was sold"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Do you think that the work ………………… by Friday?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is completed",
                        "will be completed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "These tablets ………………. with food.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "need to take",
                        "need to be taken"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The postman …………………. this letter in the morning.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "delivered",
                        "was delivered"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You ………………. the money last week.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "should sent",
                        "should have sent"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}